sourceknowledge.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy | SourceKnowledge

_Last updated_ January 9th 2019

**_Addendum_**

**GDPR COMPLIANCE**

The GDPR is a legal framework from the EU that took effect on May 25, 2018. It’s an updated version of the Data Protection Directive.

SourceKnowledge does not itself or with third parties collect, share, use, store any personally identifiable information (PII) on EU users. Personal data encompases location data, cookie ID’s IP addresses, advertising ID’s or another other identifiable or pseudonymous information.

It is SourceKnowledge’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

**ABOUT SOURCEKNOWLEDGE’S SERVICES**

SourceKnowledge provides targeted advertising services for our advertiser clients (“Advertisers”). When you visit a website operated by an Advertiser or a third party site where we could serve an ad to you, we may collect some or all of the data described in the SourceKnowledge Service Privacy Notice. Our platform uses that data as well as other data described below to help Advertisers provide ads to you that are more relevant to you.

**WHAT DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

We may collect the following categories of information for the purposes explained below. Advertiser website activity: This is data about your browsing activity on the Advertiser’s website. For example, which pages you visited and when, and what items you placed into your online shopping cart. Device and browser information: This is technical information about the device or browser you use to access the Advertiser’s website. For example, your device’s IP address, cookie string data and (in the case of mobile devices) your device type and mobile device’s unique identifier such as the Apple IDFA or Android Advertising ID. Ad data: This is data about the online ads we have served (or attempted to serve) to you. It includes things like how many times an ad has been served to you, what page the ad appeared on, and whether you clicked on or otherwise interacted with the ad. Data from Advertising Partners: This is data that we receive from other digital advertising companies that we work with (“Advertising Partners”) to help us deliver ads to you and recognize you across browsers and devices. This may include pseudonymous advertiser identifiers that some Advertisers or other third party ad platforms choose to share with us, such as your “Customer ID” with an Advertiser We may work with these Advertising Partners to synchronize their unique, anonymous identifiers to our own to enhance data points about a particular unique browser or device. We also use this data to operate, improve and enhance our services including enhancing the data points we or our Advertising Partners have about a particular user, browser, or device, or to target, optimize, cap, or synchronize advertising.

**SOURCEKNOWLEDGE APP DATA**

SourceKnowledge Shopping Ads “the App” provides access to in-market shoppers to drive new sales “the Service” to merchants who use Shopify to power their stores. This section of the Privacy Policy describes how personal information is collected, used, and shared when you install or use the App in connection with your Shopify-supported store.

Personal Information the App Collects

When you install the App, we are automatically able to access three types of information from your Shopify account:    

  1. Read_products (for collecting your product catalog)
  2. Read_script_tags (pixel placement)
  3. Write_script_tags (pixel placement)

Personal Information we collect upon download of our app: 

Additionally, we collect the following types of personal information from you and/or your customers once you have installed the App: Information about you and others who may access the App on behalf of your store, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and billing information; Information about individuals who visit your store, such as their IP address, web browser details, time zone, and information about the cookies installed on the particular device.  We also collect the following: what products the customer has viewed, what products the person has purchased, the order amounts and the order ID’s.

We collect Personal Information directly from the relevant individual, through your Shopify account, or using the following technologies: “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site. Please refer to our COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES section below for more information.

How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We use the Personal Information we collect from you and your customers in order to provide the Service and to operate the App. Additionally, we use this Personal Information to: Communicate with you; Optimize or improve the App; and Provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. We use cookie information collected on your site to target cart abandoners and for remarketing purposes.  Additionally, we share with you your customers shopping behaviour on your site. 

Sharing Your Personal Information

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

Behavioural Advertising as described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you  with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

Data Retention

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records for 90 days unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

**DATA SHARING**

We may disclose information about you: With an Advertiser whose site you have visited: We may share information about how you have interacted with that Advertiser’s site or its Ads. With our service providers: We contract with companies who help with parts of our business operations. We require that our service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for us. With service providers to our Advertisers: Our Advertisers may contract with companies who handle data (such as Advertisers’ customer lists) for them. With our subsidiaries and related companies. In connection with legal proceedings: When we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend the legal rights of SourceKnowledge, our Advertisers or any other third party. In connection with a sale of our business: If a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets, we may disclose your information in connection with the sale. We also share technical data that we collect about your browsing habits and your device (such as data relating to our cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies) with other advertising companies in the digital advertising ecosystem. This enables them and us to better target ads to you. Finally, we may disclose aggregated, anonymized information with other third parties.

**COOKIES AND RELATED TECHNOLOGIES**

The SourceKnowledge platforms uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies to provide our services for Advertisers. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. They enable us to identify your device when you move between different websites and applications, so that we can serve targeted advertising to you. Specifically, the SourceKnowledge cookie we serve through the SourceKnowledge platform is named “ProvenPixel universal pixel (upx)”. We may also drop an additional SourceKnowledge opt-out cookie if you opt-out as described below. We may also drop cookies from our Advertising Partners for the purposes described above. The Advertising Partner cookies dropped vary by Advertiser implementation.

**SOURCEKNOWLEDGE AND ADVERTISING STANDARDS**

We at SourceKnowledge comply with the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada’s (DAAC) Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising. You can learn more about the DAAC program and opt out of interest-based advertising by visiting the DAAC’s website [here](https://youradchoices.ca/).

You may have noticed the AdChoices icon  which appears on ads shown by any ad network participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance across the globe. You can access the opt out platforms by toggling “ON” via the switch below.

_Please note if you express your choice through the above platforms: when your browser blocks  third party cookies by default, you may have to first activate all cookies as explained by said platforms._

**DATA RETENTION**

Identifiable information about you is held no longer than necessary for our business purposes or to meet legal requirements.

**SECURITY**

We apply technical, administrative and organizational security measures to protect the data we collect against accidental or unlawful destruction and loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network, and against other unlawful forms of processing.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE**

Changes to this Privacy Notice will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

**CONTACT US ABOUT QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, our privacy practices, or with SourceKnowledge generally, you can contact info@sourceknowledge.com or write to us at the following address: SourceKnowledge, 1001 Boulevard de Maisonneuve West, Suite 1510 Montreal, Quebec, Canada H3A 3C8
